

Q(+1) 206-747-9888 | ■ weyjones@gmail.com | Q weyjones | in weizong-zhou | 4 weizongzhou.com

Summary

Over 2-years full-stack programmer with hands-on experience on HTML, CSS, PHP, JAVA, JavaScript, Angular.js, Swift and other popular frameworks; Passionate open-source evangelist, hackathon winner and freelance project owner; Fast learner, independent coder and outstanding team player.

Skills

Java, C, C++, Swift, HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Bash, PHP, SQL, Python Languages

Frameworks AngularJS, NodeJS, Google Firebase, Google Maps API, D3JS, MySQL, Bash Script, Git & GitHub, Salesforce Apex Emacs, IntelliJ, Eclipse, Chrome Developer Tool, Firebug, X-Code, Sublime Text, Unix Command Line, Wordpress Software

Work Experience

Providence Institute for a Healthier Community

Seattle, WA

SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

03/2017-12/2017

- · Built a website (https://pihchub.org) from scratch for helping local communities to find healthcare providers within Washington state.
- · Designed and implemented backend REST APIs using Salesforce Apex to support end-to-end search and filter functionalities in the UI.
- · Developed a responsive Wordpress custom theme and custom plugins using HTML/CSS/PHP, which support content management and publishing, user registration/login and custom save-as-favorite features.
- · Implemented a single-page web application to search and filter across 2000 health care programs efficiently using AngularJS and Google Maps API

ITravelBold.com Seattle, WA

IOS DEVELOPER INTERN

06/2016-09/2016

- Designed and developed an iOS app for connecting travelers with similar interests. Implemented the mobile front-end UI using Swift and X-code.
- · Implemented user registration, user sign-up and sign-in with OAuth2.0 and Google Firebase, sign-in via third-party identity providers with Facebook SDK.

Project Experience

Lady Problems Global Hackathon Winner

Seattle, WA

http://www.hackathon.io/speak-up

- · Developed a web dashboard using HTML, CSS and AngularJS to display real-time meeting participation data such as individual speak time and interruptions. Implemented direct viewing charts and graphs to display data using D3JS.
- · Created backend APIs using NodeJS to process and analyze real-time data streaming hosted at AWS API Gateway, AWS Lambda and DynamoDB.

Education

University of Washington, Bothell

Associate Degree of Computer Science

Bothell, WA

Bachelor of Computer Science and Software Engineering

09/2015 - 12/2017

Bellevue College

Rellevue WA

09/2012- 06/2015

Courses

Java programming language basics

Advanced Data Structure and Algorithm Analysis

Algorithms and Computational Complexity

Database System

Computer Networking

Data Structures & Algorithms, Object-Oriented Programming Programming Concepts & Tools - C, C++ Unix, Shell script, Emacs **Operating System**

Hardware & Computer Organization